lashowroom.com 2007-12-24

# LA Showroom - Privacy Policy

## LA SHOWROOM PRIVACY STATEMENT

This privacy statement covers the site WWW.LASHOWROOM.COM. This policy statement strives to explain the following issues.

  1. What personally identifiable information lashowroom.com collects.
  2. What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site.
  3. What organization collects the information.
  4. How lashowroom.com uses the information.
  5. With whom lashowroom.com may share user information.
  6. What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
  7. What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under lashowroom.com's control.
  8. How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should first contact us by phone at 213.627.0339 or by fax at 213.627.0369

## Information Collection and Use

### Information Collection

The ownership of user information collected in www.lashowroom.com is twofold. Primarily, www.lashowroom.com owns all the information collected on the site. However, as and when a user requests access to a particular store, then that store also owns that user's information. Lashowroom.com collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

### Registration

In order to use this Web site, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact the user during the course of the business transaction and to inform about new products and services on our site for which he/she has expressed interest. It is also required for the user to provide unique identifiers (such as, username and password) in order to facilitate the security concerns of the showroom owners.

### Order

We request information from the user on our checkout form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as mode of payment, credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user.

### Information Use

www.lashowroom.com is an online marketplace of apparel manufacturers and wholesalers. The information collected at the time of registration and checkout are used to carry out the primary task of facilitating a sale from the apparel manufacturer/wholesaler to the customer.

As soon as the user registers with a store or requests access to a store, his/her registration information is sent to that particular store. The store representative then can either immediately grant access to the user or contact the user for further questions/clarifications before granting access. The user can view and purchase clothing from those stores where he/she has been granted access. However, the right to cancel or grant access to any users is the sole prerogative of the store representative. Once granted access, the user will be able to access the store using his/her username and password (login information). It is the responsibility of the user and the store representative to maintain the secrecy of the username and password. Any fraudulent use of login information will lead to legal action or at the very least cancellation of access.

The website also keeps track of user statistics like date of registration, date of last visit, the number of times visited, etc. This information is used for aggregate analysis and to make business decisions. Again, the individual stores have access to this user information only if those users had requested access from them.

The user's contact information is used for the following purposes:

  1. User identity verification
  2. Communicate new products and services
  3. Communicate website information (Maintenance shutdowns, new store launch, store removals, etc)
  4. Communication during the business transaction 

The information collected at the time of checkout is used for the following purposes:

  1. Track order status during the business transaction
  2. Maintain order history
  3. Facilitate billing and shipping

www.lashowroom.com reserves the right to share the registration information with any third party that we deem is a business associate. This will only be done as a business enhancement exercise.

### Profile

We store information that we collect through the registration page, cookies, etc to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences/habits. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them. We sometimes share your profile with other third parties.

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies only. This cookie will help us in recognizing that a particular user is logged in and allow him/her to access all the stores that he/she has access to. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates.

### Log Files

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

## Communications from the Site

### Special Offers and Updates

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications in the emails themselves. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.

### Service Announcements

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.

### Customer Service

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.

## Sharing

### Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

### Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

### Third Party Intermediaries

We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

### Business Transitions

In the event lashowroom.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via email prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. If as a result of the business transition, the users' personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection they will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section.

## Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, lashowroom.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

## Security

This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information, that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just 'surfing'.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to user information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users' information is protected.

If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an email to privacy@lashowroom.com

## Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can usually be done at the My Account page available in each store. The changes made in My Account section of any store will reflect in all the store accounts of the user.

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

## Contact Information

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

**LA Showroom Inc.**  
110 E. 9th St. Ste B1201  
Los Angeles, CA 90079  
USA  
Tel: 213.627.0339  
Fax: 213.627.0369  
E-mail: customerservice@lashowroom.com
